Jensen, Vernon Collection of International Longshoremen's Association's and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Materials 5487
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-123 (1972: June 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-124 (1972: June 29)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-125 (1972: June 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-126 (1972: July 3)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-127 (1972: July 5)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-128 (1972: July 6)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-129 (1972: July 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-130 (1972: July 10)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-131 (1972: July 11)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-132 (1972: July 12)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-133 (1972: July 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-134 (1972: July 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-135 (1972: July 17)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-136 (1972: July 18)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-137 (1972: July 19)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-138 (1972: July 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-139 (1972: July 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-140 (1972: July 24)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-141 (1972: July 25)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-142 (1972: July 26)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-147 (1972: July 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-148 (1972: July 28)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.72-149 (1972: July 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-150 (1972: Aug. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-151 (1972: Aug. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-152 (1972: Aug. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-153 (1972: Aug. 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-154 (1972: Aug. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-155 (1972: Aug. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-156 (1972: Aug. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-157 (1972: Aug. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-158 (1972: Aug. 11)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-159 (1972: Aug. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-160 (1972: Aug. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-161 (1972: Aug. 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-162 (1972: Aug. 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-163 (1972: Aug. 18)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-164 (1972: Aug. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-165 (1972: Aug. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-166 (1972: Aug. 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-167 (1972: Aug. 24)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-168 (1972: Aug. 25)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-169 (1972: Aug. 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-170 (1972: Aug. 29)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-171 (1972: Aug. 30)
  - Item 23: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.72-172 (1972: Aug. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-173 (1972: Sep. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-174 (1972: Sep. 5)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-175 (1972: Sep. 6)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-176 (1972: Sep. 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-177 (1972: Sep. 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-178 (1972: Sep. 11)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-179 (1972: Sep. 12)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-180 (1972: Sep. 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-181 (1972: Sep. 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-182 (1972: Sep. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-183 (1972: Sep. 18)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-184 (1972: Sep. 19)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-185 (1972: Sep. 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-186 (1972: Sep. 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-187 (1972: Sep. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-188 (1972: Sep. 25)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-189 (1972: Sep. 26)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-190 (1972: Sep. 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-191 (1972: Sep. 28)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.72-192 (1972: Sep. 29)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-193 (1972: Oct. 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-194 (1972: Oct. 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-195 (1972: Oct. 4)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-196 (1972: Oct. 5)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-197 (1972: Oct. 6)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-198 (1972: Oct. 10)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-199 (1972: Oct. 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-200 (1972: Oct. 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-201 (1972: Oct. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-202 (1972: Oct. 16)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-203 (1972: Oct. 17)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-204 (1972: Oct. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-205 (1972: Oct. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-206 (1972: Oct. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-207 (1972: Oct. 24)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-208 (1972: Oct. 25)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-209 (1972: Oct. 26)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-210 (1972: Oct. 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-211 (1972: Oct. 30)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.72-212 (1972: Oct. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-213 (1972: Nov. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-214 (1972: Nov. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-215 (1972: Nov 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-216 (1972: Nov 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-217 (1972: Nov 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-218 (1972: Nov 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-219 (1972: Nov 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-220 (1972: Nov 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-221 (1972: Nov 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-222 (1972: Nov 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-223 (1972: Nov 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-224 (1972: Nov 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-225 (1972: Nov 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-226 (1972: Nov 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-227 (1972: Nov 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-228 (1972: Nov 24)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-229 (1972: Nov 27)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-230 (1972: Nov 28)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-231 (1972: Nov 29)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.72-232 (1972: Nov 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-233 (1972: Dec. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-234 (1972: Dec. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-235 (1972: Dec. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-236 (1972: Dec. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-237 (1972: Dec. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-238 (1972: Dec. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-239 (1972: Dec. 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-240 (1972: Dec. 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-241 (1972: Dec. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-242 (1972: Dec. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-243 (1972: Dec. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-244 (1972: Dec. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-245 (1972: Dec. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-246 (1972: Dec. 20)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-247 (1972: Dec. 21)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-248 (1972: Dec. 26)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-249 (1972: Dec. 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.72-250 (1972: Dec. 28)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-1 (1973: Jan. 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-2 (1973: Jan. 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-3 (1973: Jan. 4)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-4 (1973: Jan. 5)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-5 (1973: Jan. 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-6 (1973: Jan. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-7 (1973: Jan. 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-8 (1973: Jan. 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-9 (1973: Jan. 12)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-10 (1973: Jan. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-11 (1973: Jan. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-12 (1973: Jan. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-13 (1973: Jan. 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-14 (1973: Jan. 19)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-15 (1973: Jan. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-16 (1973: Jan. 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-17 (1973: Jan. 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-18 (1973: Jan. 25)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-19 (1973: Jan. 26)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-20 (1973: Jan. 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-21 (1973: Jan. 30)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.73-22 (1973: Jan. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-23 (1973: Feb. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-24 (1973: Feb. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-25 (1973: Feb. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-26 (1973: Feb. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-27 (1973: Feb. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-28 (1973: Feb. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-29 (1973: Feb. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-30 (1973: Feb. 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-31 (1973: Feb. 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-32 (1973: Feb. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-33 (1973: Feb. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-34 (1973: Feb. 20)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-35 (1973: Feb. 21)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-36 (1973: Feb. 22)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-37 (1973: Feb. 23)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-38 (1973: Feb. 26)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-39 (1973: Feb. 27)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.73-40 (1973: Feb. 28)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-41 (1973: Mar. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-42 (1973: Mar. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-43 (1973: Mar. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-44 (1973: Mar. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-45 (1973: Mar. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-46 (1973: Mar. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-47 (1973: Mar. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-47 (1973: Mar. 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-48 (1973: Mar. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-49 (1973: Mar. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-50 (1973: Mar. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-51 (1973: Mar. 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-52 (1973: Mar. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-53 (1973: Mar. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-54 (1973: Mar. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-55 (1973: Mar. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-56 (1973: Mar. 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-57 (1973: Mar. 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-58 (1973: Mar. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-59 (1973: Mar. 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-60 (1973: Mar. 29)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.73-61 (1973: Mar. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-62 (1973: Apr. 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-63 (1973: Apr. 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-64 (1973: Apr. 4)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-65 (1973: Apr. 5)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-66 (1973: Apr. 6)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-67 (1973: Apr. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-68 (1973: Apr. 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-69 (1973: Apr. 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-70 (1973: Apr. 12)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-71 (1973: Apr. 13)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-72 (1973: Apr. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-73 (1973: Apr. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-74 (1973: Apr. 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-75 (1973: Apr. 19)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-67 (1973: Apr. 23)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-68 (1973: Apr. 24)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-69 (1973: Apr. 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-70 (1973: Apr. 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-71 (1973: Apr. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.73-72 (1973: Apr. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-73 (1973: May 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-74 (1973: May 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-75 (1973: May 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-76 (1973: May 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-77 (1973: May 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-78 (1973: May 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-79 (1973: May 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-80 (1973: May 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-81 (1973: May 11)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-82 (1973: May 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-83 (1973: May 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-84 (1973: May 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-85 (1973: May 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-85 (1973: May 18)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-86 (1973: May 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-87 (1973: May 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-88 (1973: May 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-89 (1973: May 24)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-90 (1973: May 25)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-91 (1973: May 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-92 (1973: May 30)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.73-93 (1973: May 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-94 (1973: June 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-95 (1973: June 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-96 (1973: June 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-97 (1973: June 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-98 (1973: June 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-99 (1973: June 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-100 (1973: June 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-101 (1973: June 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-102 (1973: June 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-103 (1973: June 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-104 (1973: June 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-105 (1973: June 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-106 (1973: June 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-107 (1973: June 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-108 (1973: June 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-109 (1973: June 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-110 (1973: June 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-111 (1973: June 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-112 (1973: June 27)